And then every day, smart, interesting twentysomethings, like you or like your sons and daughters
每一天   像你或你们儿子女儿一样的聪明   有趣的二十几岁的人​
come into my office and say things like this:
到我办公室   说这些话
"I know my boyfriend's no good for me, but this relationship doesn't count. I'm just killing time. "
我知道我男朋友不太合适我   但这段关系不算数   我只是在打发时间
Or they say, " Everybody says as long as I get started on a career by the time I'm 30. I'll be fine. "
或者他们说   每个人都说只要我在30岁前开始我的事业   就没问题
But then it starts to sound like this:
渐渐地   开始变成这样​
"My 20s are almost over, and I have nothing to show for myself.
我都快30岁了   我没有什么拿得出手的​
I had a better resume the day after I graduated from college. "
我毕业时的简历都比现在要好
And then it starts to sound like this:
再后来就变成这样​
"Dating in my 20s was like musical chairs, everybody was running around and having fun,
二十几岁约会时就像玩抢椅子游戏   大家都在跑都在玩​
but then sometime around 30 it was like the music turned off and everybody started sitting down.
但到30岁的时候就像音乐停止   每个人都开始坐下
I didn't want to be the only one left standing up, so sometimes I think I married my husband
我不想成为唯一一个站着的人   所以我有时在想我嫁给我老公​
because he was the closest chair to me at 30. "
是因为在我30岁时离我最近的椅子
Where are the twentysomethings is here? Do not do that.
在座的二十几岁的人在哪里   千万不要那样做